Guide to the Charles Seymour Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1912-(1918-1922)-1963; Series I; 7'4" (20 boxes)
  - General Correspondence
    - Langrock, David T., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 488a)
    - Lansing, Robert, 1918-1919, 1925-1928, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 489)
    - Larsen, J. A., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 490)
    - Larsen, William, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 491)
    - Léon, Maurice, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 492)
    - Latham, Earl, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 493)
    - Latourette, Kenneth S., 1950, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 494)
    - Lawrence, Kelvyn H., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 495)
    - Learned, H. Barrett, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 496)
    - Lederer, Ivo J., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 497)
    - Leffingwell, R. C., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 498)
    - Lentz, Rex V., 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 499)
    - Quarré, Pierre, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 500)
      See also: box 64, folder 119
    - l'Epine, Captain de, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 501)
    - Levine, I. M., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 502)
    - Lewis, Howard B., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 503)
    - Lewis, Wilmarth S., 1954, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 504)
    - Lewiston Daily Sun, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 505)
    - Light, Richard U., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 506)
    - Lindsay, Mrs. Thomas, n.y. (Box 9, Folder 507)
    - Linehan, William D.
    - Lingley, Charles R., 1923, 1926, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 508)
    - Lininger, Fred T.
    - Link, Arthur, 1952-1957, 1959, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 509)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 12/5
    - Lipphard, William B., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 510)
    - Lippmann, Walter, 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 511)
    - Littleton Stamp Company, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 512)
    - Lloyd George, David, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 513)
    - Lockman, John Q., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 514)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 515)
    - Loman, May H. (Mrs. John), 1950 (Box 9, Folder 516)
    - Long, Hamilton A., 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 517)
    - Long, Hamilton A., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 518)
    - Longmans, Green and Company
      See: box 14, folder 848-869 box 12, folder 717-718
    - Loram, Charles T., 1935-1937, undated (Box 9, Folder 519)
    - Loram, Hilda V., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 520)
    - Lord, Robert H.
    - Lorenz, William A., 1926 (Box 9, Folder 521)
    - Lothian, Lord (Philip Kerr), 1933 (Box 9, Folder 522)
    - Loukas, Chryst
      See: box 1, folder 35
    - Lounsbury, Ralph G., 1935 (Box 9, Folder 523)
    - Lovett, Sidney, 1949-1950, 1956, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 524)
    - Low, Richard E.
    - Lowell, A. Lawrence, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 525)
    - Lowes, Joseph E., Jr., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 526)
    - Lowitt, Ricard, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 527)
    - Ludwig, Emil, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 528)
    - Lull, Richard S.
    - Luther, C. Fisher, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 529)
    - Lutz, Ralph, 1926, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 530)
    - Lutz, Ralph, 1933-1934, 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 531)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 10/8
    - Lyon, William H., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 532)
    - Lyons, Maurice F., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 533)
    - McAdoo, William G., 1925 (Box 9, Folder 534)
    - McCills, Kenneth T., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 535)
    - McClendon, James
    - McClure, S. S., 1923 (Box 9, Folder 536)
    - McCook, Anson T., 1949, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 537)
      See also: box 3, folder 151
    - MacCormick, Austin H., 1923 (Box 9, Folder 538)
    - McCormick, Vance C.
      See: box 84, folder 25
      See also: The Papers of Vance McCormick, MS 478
    - McDonald, James G.
      See: George W. Watt (1947 Oct 2), box 15, folder 889
    - McDonnell, Hubert
    - McDougal, Myres S., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 539)
    - MacGregor, D. A., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 540)
    - McGuirk, Katherine, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 541)
    - MacIver, R. M., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 542)
    - McLaren, Walter W.
      See: box 8, folder 441
    - Macmillan Company, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 543)
    - McNulty, Arthur P., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 544)
    - McReynolds, J. C., 1914, undated (Box 9, Folder 545)
    - Mallory, Philip R., 1950, 1952-1953, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 546)
    - Manning, F.G., 1917 (Box 9, Folder 546a)
    - Malott, Deane W.
      See: box 4, folder 190
    - Mantoux, J. A., 1963 (Box 9, Folder 547)
    - Mantoux, Mathilde, 1958, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 548)
    - Marsh, Daniel L., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 549)
    - Martin, Edwin L., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 550)
    - Martin, Geoffrey J., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 551)
    - Martin, Laurence W., 1956 - 1957 June (Box 9, Folder 552)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 12/2
    - Martin, Laurence W., 1957 September - 1958 (Box 9, Folder 553)
    - Mason, Julian S.
      See: box 10, folder 599-601
    - Mathewson, Champion H., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 554)
    - Mayer, Arno J., 1952, 1954, 1956, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 555)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 12/3
    - Mayo, H. T.
    - Melish, J. H., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 556)
    - Mendell, Clarence W., 1927, 1952, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 557)
    - Mendenhall, Thomas C., 1952-1953, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 558)
      See also: box 11, folder 692
    - Merrels, Frederick B., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 559)
    - Merrill, Mary G., 1917 (Box 9, Folder 559a)
    - Merriman, Daniel, 1949, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 560)
    - Messerly, C. E., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 561)
    - Merz, Charles, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 562)
    - Mezes, Sidney E., 1921-1923, 1926, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 563)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 13/7
    - Middlebury College
      See: box 12, folder 792
    - Milbank, Jeremiah
    - Miles, Walter R., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 564)
    - Millard, A., 1925 (Box 10, Folder 565)
    - Millard, C. I., 1929 (Box 10, Folder 566)
    - Miller, David H., 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 567)
      See also: box 1, folder 1-11 box 4, folder 239-240 boxes 21-43
    - Miller, E. I., 1929 (Box 10, Folder 568)
    - Miller, Franklin, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 568a)
    - Miller, George D.
      See: box 7, folder 390 box 10, folder 639
    - Miller, L. Vernon, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 569)
    - Millis, Walter, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 570)
    - Mills, Edward E.
    - Mills, Eugene S., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 571)
    - Mills, Joan P.
    - Mills, L. H., 1928 (Box 10, Folder 572)
    - Mims, Stewart L., 1922 (Box 10, Folder 573)
    - Minnesota, University of, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 574)
    - Minnigerode, Mead, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 574a)
    - Miswald, Norman L., 1926 (Box 10, Folder 575)
    - Mitchell, Hobart, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 575a)
    - Mitchell, Mark L., 1958 (Box 10, Folder 576)
    - Mitchell, Sidney K., 1917 (Box 10, Folder 576a)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 0/3
    - Mitchell, Stewart, 1938-1940 (Box 10, Folder 577)
    - Moe, H. A.
    - Moore, John W., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 578)
    - Moore, Paul, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 579)
    - Morison, S. E., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 580)
    - Morris, Charles G., 1956 (Box 10, Folder 581)
    - Morris, Robert T., 1938 (Box 10, Folder 582)
    - Morse, Jarvis M., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 583)
    - Morse, John B., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 584)
    - Morse, S. F. B., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 585)
    - Mory's, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 586)
    - Moseley, Laura (Mrs. Nicholas), 1939 (Box 10, Folder 587)
    - Munson, Craig D.
    - Murphy, Robert C.
    - Murray, Arthur, 1933, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 588)
    - Musser, John M., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 589)
    - Myers, Leroy R., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 590)
    - Myers, Walter, 1960-1961, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 591)
    - Mystic Seaport
      See: box 9, folder 546
    - Nagel, Charles, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 592)
    - Nakahara, Mickey, [1947] (Box 10, Folder 593)
    - Neal, Homer C., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 594)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1928, 1935, 1950, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 595)
    - New Haven, City of, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 596)
    - New Mexico, University of, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 597)
    - New York Evening Post, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 598)
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1925-1926, 1960 August (Box 10, Folder 599)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 7/8
      See also: box 11, folder 684-686
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1960 September-October (Box 10, Folder 600)
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1961, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 601)
    - New York Times, [1927?] (Box 10, Folder 602)
    - Newell, F. H., 1927 (Box 10, Folder 603)
    - News and Courier
      See: box 12, folder 772-774 box 14, folder 872
    - Nichols, C. A., Company, 1919, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 604)
    - Nickerson, Joshua, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 605)
    - Nicolson, Harold, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 606)
      See also: Books, "Letters from the Paris Peace Conference," boxes 44-46
      See also: box 53, folder 325
    - Niles, Charles H.
      See: box 4, folder 183
    - Nitti, Francesco, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 607)
    - Norris, Frank Ely, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 608)
    - North, Oliver B., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 609)
    - Northcliffe, Viscount, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 610)
    - Norton, William B., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 611)
    - Notestein, Wallace, 1955, 1958, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 612)
    - Noyes, Edward S., 1952-1953 (Box 10, Folder 613)
    - Noyes, Margaret P., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 614)
    - Noyes, Robert H., 1926, 1947, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 615)
    - Nyman, R. Carter, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 616)
    - Oakes, George W. Ochs, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 617)
    - Ochs, George Washington, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 617a)
    - O'Connor, William J.
    - Olds, Evelyn F., 1957 (Box 10, Folder 618)
    - Olds, Irving S., 1949-1950, 1955, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 619)
    - Olds, Marshall, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 619a)
    - O'Neal, Emmet, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 620)
    - Ordway, Philip S., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 621)
    - Osborn, G. C., 1957 (Box 10, Folder 622)
    - Osborn, Minott A., 1922, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 623)
    - O'Sullivan, Patrick B., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 624)
    - Otlet, M. P., 1924 (Box 10, Folder 625)
    - Ottemiller, John H., 1957 (Box 10, Folder 626)
    - Overbergh, Carl, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 627)
    - Owen, W. H., 1923 (Box 10, Folder 628)
    - Paderewski, I. J., 1928 (Box 10, Folder 629)
    - Page, Arthur W., 1925-1926 (Box 10, Folder 630)
    - Page, W. H.
    - Paradise, Mrs. N. Burton, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 631)
    - Parks, Stephen, n.y. (Box 10, Folder 632)
    - Parmer, J. Norman, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 633)
    - Parsons, Myra, 1953
    - Parsons, Sarah, n.y.
    - Parsons, Seymour, 1961
    - Pasquariello, Paul, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 636)
    - Pauling, Linus, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 637)
    - Peabody, George F., 1925 (Box 10, Folder 638)
    - Peltz, W. L. L., 1950, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 639)
      See also: box 7, folder 390
    - Pennsylvania, University of, Law Review, 1922-1923 (Box 10, Folder 640)
    - Perkins, Maxwell
    - Perkins, Thomas N., 1927 (Box 10, Folder 641)
    - Perrin, Lester W., 1924, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 642)
    - Perry, Bliss
    - Perry, Thomas S., 1926 (Box 10, Folder 643)
    - Pershing, John J. (Box 10, Folder 644)
    - Petain, Henri Philippe, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 645)
    - Peyre, Henri, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 646)
    - Pflieger, Robert P., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 647)
    - Pforzheimer, Walter L., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 648)
    - Phelps, William L. (Box 11, Folder 649)
      See also: box 4, folder 201 box 10, folder 643
    - Philadelphia Record, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 650)
    - Phillips, Duncan, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 651)
    - Phillips, Marion L., 1920 (Box 11, Folder 652)
    - Phillips, William, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 653)
    - Pickhardt, Otto C., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 654)
    - Pickrel, Paul, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 655)
    - Pierson, George W., 1952 - 1953 July (Box 11, Folder 656)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 8/0
      See also: box 6, folder 323 box 9, folder 552-553
    - Pierson, George W., 1953 August-December (Box 11, Folder 657)
    - Pierson, George W., 1954 May-August (Box 11, Folder 658)
    - Pierson, George W., 1954 October - 1955 (Box 11, Folder 659)
    - Pierson, George W., 1957-1958, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 660)
    - Pigott, John T., 1959, undated (Box 11, Folder 661)
    - Pirenne, Henri, 1922, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 662)
    - Planned Parenthood of Connecticut, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 663)
    - Platzer, Wilfried, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 664)
    - Plunkett, Sit Horace, 1925-1928 (Box 11, Folder 665)
      See also: box 52, folder 265
    - Polish Institute of Arts and Sciences in America, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 666)
    - Political Science Quarterly, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 667)
    - Polk, Frank, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 668)
      See also: The Frank L. Polk Papers, MS 656
    - Poole, Lynn
    - Pope, Liston, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 669)
    - Porter, Graham, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 670)
    - Post, Avery D., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 671)
    - Potter, David, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 672)
    - Pottle, Essie K., 1954 (Box 11, Folder 673)
    - Pratt, Julius W., 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 674)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 4/5
    - Price, Lucien, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 675)
    - Proctor, William R., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 676)
    - Pruden, Russell G., 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 677)
      See also: box 15, folder 917 box 15, folder 886-892
    - Tardieu, André, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 678)
    - Rafferty, Max
    - Rahder, Johannes, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 679)
    - Raiga, Eugène, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 680)
    - Ratcliffe, Samuel K., 1926 (Box 11, Folder 681)
      See also: box 52, folder 267
    - Read, Conyers, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 682)
    - Reading, Lord (Rufus D. Isaacs), 1928 (Box 11, Folder 683)
    - Reid Foundation, 1952-1955 (Box 11, Folder 684)
    - Reid Foundation, 1956 April-October (Box 11, Folder 685)
    - Reid Foundation, 1956 November - 1959 (Box 11, Folder 686)
    - Reid, Helen Rogers, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 687)
    - Reid, Whitelaw
    - Reigeluth, Ray J., 1920, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 688)
    - Renouvin, P.
    - Reut-Nicolussi, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 689)
    - Reynolds, Helen, 1926-1927 (Box 11, Folder 690)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 17/14
    - Reynolds, Helen, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 691)
    - Reynolds, James B.
      See: box 2, folder 102
    - Rhodes Committee (Connecticut), 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 692)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 9/3
    - Richards, Marie
    - Richardson, Genevieve W. (Mrs. Egbert), 1950 (Box 11, Folder 693)
    - Rickard, Edgar
    - Riker, Thaddeus W., 1917 (Box 11, Folder 693a)
    - Riley, Henry A., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 694)
    - Ripley, Julien A., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 695)
    - Robbins, Frank, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 696)
    - Robbins, John C., Jr.
    - Robertson, A. Clendenin, 1954, 1957, 1959, undated (Box 11, Folder 697)
    - Robinson, Chalfont, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 697a)
    - Robinson, Geroid T., 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 698)
    - Robison, Paul G., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 699)
    - Rockefeller Foundation
    - Rogers, Lindsay, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 700)
    - Rogers, Orville F., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 701)
    - Rollins College
      See: box 7, folder 404
    - Roosevelt House Library and Museum, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 702)
    - Root, Edward C., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 703)
    - Root, Elihu, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 704)
    - Rosemary Hall, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 705)
    - Rosen, Gustave J., 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 706)
    - Rostow, Eugene V., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 707)
    - Royal Historical Society, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 708)
    - Rudin, Harry R.
    - Rumanian and Yugoslav Commission
    - Rust, Schuyler, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 709)
    - Ryan, John H., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 710)
    - Ryerson, Edward L., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 711)
    - St. Clair, Grady, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 712)
    - St. John, Clara Seymour (Mrs. George), 1924, 1937, 1950
    - St. John, George, 1924
    - Saltonstall, Leverett, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 715)
    - Sanders, John E., 1959 (Box 12, Folder 716)
    - Sanford, Brad
    - Sargent, Dwight E.
    - Sarkissian, A. O., 1959 - 1960 August (Box 12, Folder 717)
    - Sarkissian, A. O., 1960 September - 1961 (Box 12, Folder 718)
    - Sato, Aimaro, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 719)
    - Savage, Henry L., 1956 (Box 12, Folder 720)
    - Sawyer, Charles, n.y. (Box 12, Folder 721)
    - Saxon, O. Glenn, Testimonial Dinner Committee, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 722)
    - Saybrook College, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 723)
    - Scaife, Roger
    - Schilling, Walter, 1953-1956 (Box 12, Folder 724)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 9/5
    - Schirmer, Robert, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 724a)
    - Schley, Kate (Mrs. Reeve), 1957, undated (Box 12, Folder 725)
    - Schmitt, Bernadotte E., 1933, 1947, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 726)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 1/5
    - Scholle, Will, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 727)
    - Schreiber, Carl F., 1926 (Box 12, Folder 728)
    - Schroeder, John C., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 729)
    - Schuschnigg, Walter
      See: box 7, folder 384a
    - Schuyler, Robert Livingston
    - Schwabe, Klaus, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 730)
    - Scott, James B.
    - Scott, Karen (Mrs. James F.), 1953 (Box 12, Folder 731)
    - Scott, William E., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 732)
    - Scranton, Margery (Mrs. Worthington), 1950 (Box 12, Folder 733)
    - Scribner, Charles
    - Seabury, Paul, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 734)
    - Sedgwick, Ellery
      See: box 1, folder 38
    - Sedgwick, Hubert M., 1926 (Box 12, Folder 735)
    - Segal, Max M., 1930 (Box 12, Folder 736)
    - Seligman, Joseph L., 1923 (Box 12, Folder 737)
    - Seligmann, George A., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 738)
    - Sewall, Richard B., 1958 (Box 12, Folder 739)
    - Seymour, Charles, Jr.
      See: box 8, folder 460
    - Seymour, Elizabeth, n.y.
    - Seymour, Fannie E. (Mrs. Henry I.), 1940, 1943
    - Seymour, George D., 1926, 1936
    - Seymour, Ruth [Beth], 1908
    - Shackleton, Robert A., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 744)
    - Shelley, George E.
    - Shepard, Roger B., 1958 (Box 12, Folder 745)
    - Sheppard, John T.
    - Sherrill, Henry K., [1949], [1954] (Box 12, Folder 746)
    - Shotwell, James T.
      See: box 4, folder 239-240
      See: Books, "The Intimate Papers of Colonel House," boxes 21-43
      See: The Inquiry Papers, MS 8
    - Sias, Garrett K.
      See: box 13, folder 826
    - Sickel, Lucien J., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 747)
    - Sills, Kenneth C. M.
      See: box 2, folder 104
    - Silver, Burdette, and Company, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 748)
    - Silverman, O. A., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 749)
    - Simpson, Hartley, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 750)
    - Sims, William S., 1919 (Box 12, Folder 751)
    - Sinclair, Gregg M., 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 752)
    - Sinnott, Edmund W., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 753)
    - Sizer, Theodore, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 754)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 6/0
    - Skinner, James H., 1925 (Box 12, Folder 755)
    - Small, John H., Jr., 1926 (Box 12, Folder 756)
    - Smith, Arthur D. Howden, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 757)
    - Smith, Courtney
      See: box 11, folder 692
    - Smith, Evelyn (Mrs. Richard)
    - Smith, Richard
      See: box 3, folder 159-163 box 15, folder 892
    - Smith, Robinson, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 758)
    - Smucker, Edwin M., 1926 (Box 12, Folder 759)
    - Smyth, Charles
      See: box 3, folder 136
    - Snavely, Harry E.
      See: box 16, folder 932
    - Snyder, Phil L., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 760)
    - Social Science Research Council
    - Soulsby, Hugh B., 1929 (Box 12, Folder 761)
    - Sparhawk, William N., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 762)
    - Speyer, Henri, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 763)
    - Speyer, James, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 764)
    - Spindler, Arno, 1933 September 12 (Box 12, Folder 765)
    - Spindler, Arno, 1935 November 4 (Box 12, Folder 766)
    - Spindler, Arno, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 767)
    - Spindler, Arno, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 768)
    - Spivack, R.G., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 768a)
    - Splawn, Walter M. W., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 769)
    - Spring-Rice, Florence (Lady Spring-Rice), 1925 (Box 12, Folder 770)
    - Spring-Rice, Thomas, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 771)
    - Squires, J. Duane
      See: box 15, folder 875-877
    - Stanley, Harold, 1928, 1935, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 772)
      See also: Andrew Keogh, box 8, folder 468
      See also: Pegler Articles, box 64, folder 120
      See also: Series IV, Memorabilia
    - Stanley, Harold, 1917, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 773)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 8/2
    - Stanley, Harold (obituary), 1959-1961 (Box 12, Folder 774)
    - Stanley, Maurice, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 775)
    - Stapler, Henry B., 1937 (Box 12, Folder 776)
    - Starr, Louis, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 777)
    - Staton, Harry
    - Steed, H. Wickham, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 778)
      See also: box 52, folder 265 box 64, folder 119
    - Steffens, Lincoln, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 779)
    - Steinman, James H., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 780)
    - Stettinius, Edward
    - Stevens, Frederick N., undated (Box 12, Folder 781)
    - Stevenson, E. Robert, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 782)
    - Stevenson, George S., 1956 (Box 12, Folder 783)
    - Stewart, Calder B., 1950, 1955, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 784)
    - Stewart, George, 1950, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 785)
    - Stimson, Mabel W., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 785a)
    - Stiles, D. A.
    - Stillman, P. Gordon B.
    - Stoddard, Henry L., 1926 (Box 12, Folder 786)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1926, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 787)
    - Stokes, Frederick A., 1925 (Box 12, Folder 788)
    - Stokes, Harold Phelps, 1923, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 789)
    - Stone, Louis T., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 790)
    - Storey, Moorfield, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 791)
    - Stratton, Samuel S., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 792)
    - Street, Julian, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 793)
    - Strong, Benjamin, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 794)
    - Strong, Henry B., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 795)
    - Stroud, Joe H., 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 796)
    - Stuart, Campbell, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 797)
    - Sturges, Wesley A., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 798)
    - Sullivan, Leonard, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 799)
    - Swain, Henry L., 1922 (Box 12, Folder 800)
    - Swenson, S. M., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 801)
    - Swinney, Edward B., 1926 (Box 12, Folder 802)
    - Sylvester, A. J.
      See: box 9, folder 513
    - Taft, William H., 1917 (Box 12, Folder 802a)
    - Talcott, Mary K., 1912
    - Portion of Les Antécedents Diplomatiques de la Guerre 1870-1914, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 804)
    - Taylor, Effie J., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 805)
    - Terrell, C. V.
    - Texas State Historical Society
    - Thomas, John, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 806)
    - Thompson, H. Keith, 1957, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 807)
    - Thompson, Mackey J., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 808)
    - Thomson, Harry C.
    - Thomson, James C., Jr., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 809)
    - Tilson, Vernon V., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 810)
    - Torrey, Charles C., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 811)
    - Toussaint, Fernand
      See: box 4, folder 178
    - Townsend, George H., 1920, 1950, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 812)
      See also: box 3, folder 159-163 box 15, folder 908
    - Townsend, Vera (Mrs. George)
    - Treat, P. J., 1923 (Box 13, Folder 813)
    - Trinity College, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 814)
    - Truman, Harry S., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 814a)
    - Tschan, Dr. Francis J., 1917 (Box 13, Folder 814b)
    - Tuck, H. Hallam, 1926, 1936, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 815)
    - Tucker, Mona House (Mrs. Randolph), 1931, 1938, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 816)
    - Tucker, Robert L., 1948 (Box 13, Folder 817)
    - Tufts, Nathan, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 818)
    - Tully, L. L., 1921 (Box 13, Folder 819)
    - Tumulty, Joseph P., 1920 (Box 13, Folder 820)
    - Tuttle, Henry C., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 821)
    - Twenhofel, W. H., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 822)
    - Twombly, Edward B.
      See: box 3, folder 164
    - Udale, Stanley M., 1957 (Box 13, Folder 823)
    - Uhlmann, Michael M.
      See: box 12, folder 722
    - Underwood, Kennard, 1937, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 824)
    - United Nations - Office of Personnel, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 825)
    - United States Information Agency, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 826)
    - United States Treasury Department
    - Urban, Wilbur M., 1937 (Box 13, Folder 827)
    - Vail, Robert W. G.
      See: box 11, folder 702
    - Van Alstyne, Richard W., 1942 (Box 13, Folder 828)
    - Vance, W. S., 1955 (Box 13, Folder 829)
    - Van Cleve, Thomas C., 1923 (Box 13, Folder 830)
    - Van Doren, A. Reading, Jr., 1952 (Box 13, Folder 831)
    - Van Pelt, David, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 832)